

## CONTACT

paabloo.ch@gmail.com

+34 655 072 165

Barcelona, Spain

Pablo Cebollada Hernández

paablooch.github.io

PaablooCH

#### **PROJECTS**

Axolotl Engine - Starfall Rebellion

Megaman Game 2D-Plataform

Undercooked 3D-Unity-Puzzle

Deus Ex Machina In-house Engine

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

C++







Visual Studio



**NSight** 



Git



RenderDoc



Jira



Unity

## SOFT SKILLS

Dynamic worker

Quick learner

Critical thinker

Problem solver

Adaptable and flexible person

Reliable team member, with a strong work ethic

# LANGUAGES

Spanish Native

Catalan Native

English Professional working proficiency

# PABLO CEBOLLADA

#### RENDER PROGRAMMER

#### PROFILE

I'm a junior programmer, with a strong background in the creation of applications and a passion for graphics programming. I have experience in developing 2D video games using a non-commercial engine. I've also worked on 3D game development using Unity. Recently, I focused on graphics development for my final master project. This involved creating and using shaders with OpenGL and deepening my proficiency in the C++ language.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Render & Engine Programmer (Master's project)

Horizons Games

January 2023-Present

- I've developed a series of features in the rendering system of the engine, which include the utilization of various shaders for different rendering purposes. In addition, I've contributed to both engine and gameplay features and reviewed
- I possess a solid understanding of C++ and rendering techniques, as well as a comprehensive knowledge of the game development life cycle.

# **Software Developer**

IThink UPC

February 2022-February 2023

- I worked as a full stack developer, developing web applications for third parties.
- This involved collaborating in large, multidisciplinary teams.
- I utilized the Scrum methodology along with Jira for project management.
- I learned strong communication skills to interact effectively with customers.
- Additionally, I gained experience in implementing various programming patterns.

## Software Developer (Internship)

Telespazio Ibérica

April 2021-January 2022

- I worked as a full stack developer, developing web applications for first party.
- · I consistently met all client-set deadlines.
- Additionally, I use the Scrum methodology for efficient project management.

### EDUCATION

## Master in Advanced Programming for AAA Videogames

Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya - UPC BarcelonaTech - Talent School 2022 - 2023

# **Degree in Computer Science**

Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya - UPC BarcelonaTech 2017 - 2022

#### HOBBIES

I spend my spare time mostly playing video games, especially shooters and MOBAs, but recently, I've started playing JRPGs like Persona 5, and survival horrors like Signalis. Additionally, I like to read papers about rendering techniques to keep myself updated and I set aside time to practice some sports.